

Contact

Phone

+375 29 315 10 26

Email

olg.grishchenko@gmail.com

Telegram

@OlgGrishchenko

GitHub

<u>LinkedIn</u>

Education

September 2023 - now

English tutor

• B1 in progress

April 2022 - January 2023

TeachMeSkills

• Frontend Developer

2009-2013

Belarusian State Economic University

• Economic Sociology

Hard skills

- React
- React Router DOM
- Redux Toolkit
- Redux-Saga
- Apisauce
- TypeScript, JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS, SCSS
- Bootstrap
- GIT
- Figma
- VS Code
- English A2

Olga Grishchenko

About me:

As a former event planner, I love challenges - and frontend development sounds like a great one.

Event planning experience made me a team player, taught me to work under strict deadlines and search for unexpected solutions. And I feel that these skills should help me become an outstanding frontend developer, along with lots of hard work of course.

In my spare time, I enjoy travelling as every trip is a new exciting challenge.

Work experience

O December 2022 - now Frontend developer

Agile Dreamers

As a top-3 student, I was invited to an internship to work in an ongoing project for Project and Client Management Application development.

Responsibilities:

- Setting up the project environment
- Participated in the creation of pages and components
- Code review of the project
- Interaction with the server part of the application (API)
- Learning new React libraries: Ant Design, International Telephone Input and etc.

Stack: React, Redux, Redux-Saga, Apisauce, TypeScript, JavaScript, Ant Design, ESlint.

April 2022 - January 2023 Frontend developer (graduate)

TeachMeSkills

Skills:

- · Knowledge of Git
- Cross-browser and adaptive layout on HTML/CSS/SCSS
- Knowledge of JavaScript
- Development experience in React: Apisauce, Redux Toolkit, Redux-Saga
- Confident knowledge of TypeScript.

Within the training courses I created several apps:

Pixema

Stack: JavaScript, React, Redux, Redux-Saga, Apisauce; Used TypeScript for best code control; Deploying.

Link to GitHub

Blogofolio

Stack: JavaScript, React, Redux, Redux-Saga, Apisauce;

Used TypeScript for best code control; Deploying.

Link to GitHub

- ToDo App Link to GitHub
- Trello App Link to GitHub

Stack: JavaScript, HTML, CSS.

- ActiveBox (layout) Link to GitHub
- AXIT (layout) Link to GitHub

2015 - 2022

Wedding Planner, Founder

WeddinGo Agency

Results:

- Built a business from scratch
- Planned and coordinated 30-40 events annually weddings, family events,
- · fashion shows both in and outside of Belarus
- As part of the business, I created a school for event coordinators and
- mentored new event planners